Ah, uniforms.
あら、制服
It suits you.
似合うね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Oh my, that's cute.
やべ、可愛いね
How old are you now?
今、いくつだっけ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
I just graduated.
卒業しただけやん
I graduated.
卒業しました
What did the uniform look like?
どんな感じの制服だったの?
Is this it?
これか?
blazer?
ブレザー?
It was.
でした
Do you feel similar?
似てるような感じ?
You look good in the uniform, after all.
制服似合うね、やっぱね
That's why I was wearing it.
着 てたわけだもんね
Did you have sex the other day, and have you had any sex since then?
この間エッチして、あれから何かエッチしたりした?
I haven't.
してないね
Really?
本当に?
how was it?
どうだった?
The previous sex.
前のエッチは
It was fun.
楽しかったです
it was fun?
楽しかった?
TRUE?
本当?
good.
よかった
Did you do anything fun recently?
最近何か楽しいことあった?
I played.
遊びました
Did you go on a trip?
旅行行ったの?
Where have you been?
どこ行ってきたの?
I went to my house.
家に行ってきました
nice.
いいね
I've been playing.
遊んできたんだ
Aren't you with your boyfriend?
彼氏とじゃないの?
It's a girl's friend.
女の子の友達ですよ
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなの?
nice.
いいね
It looked like this, of socks.
こんな感じだった、靴下の
I just graduated.
卒業したてだもんね
Almost...
ほぼ...
good?
いい?
Favorite uncle?
好きなおじさん?
What do you think?
どうだって思うかも
Do you think it's okay?
大丈夫かなと思う?
All the old men in this world...
この世のおじさんはみんな...
I like it.
好きなんだよ
Did you know?
知ってた?
It's a bit dangerous, isn't it?
ちょっとやばいよね
Among my favorites...
好きの中でも...
Best of...
ベストオブ...
There's someone I like.
好きな人がいるんだけど
I was listening...
聞いてたんですけど...
...
As cute as it looks
見えるくらい可愛い
That's right.
ですね
The old man wears too many uniforms...
お じさん制服を着過ぎてさ...
Can't you contain your excitement?
興奮が抑えられないんでしょうか
amazing.
すごい
good?
いい?
Isn't she really an angel?
めちゃくちゃ天使じゃないですか
How tall are you?
身長は?
Height is 145cm.
身長は145センチ
145cm?
145センチ?
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらってもいい?
A little like a doll...
ちょっとお人形さんみたいな...
What do you think?
どうだろう?
I don't know.
分かんない
Even my uncle thinks it's dangerous.
おじさん自分でもやばいと思うんですけど
It might be dangerous.
やばいかもじゃあ
It's no good if you have a strong belly button.
ヘソが強いのダメ
No belly button?
ヘソがダメ?
I understand, I understand.
分かった分かった
Uncles don't say no.
おじさんってダメって言うことしないから
Such a child...
こういう子ね...
I wanted to cuddle on the train...
電車の中でギューってやりたかったんだけど...
It's cute.
可愛いね
Really.
本当にね
My uncle's face was also shown.
おじさん顔も出しちゃった
I did it with a black tongue.
黒い舌でやった
I did it with my sexy tongue.
セクシーな舌でやった
Today happened to be.
今日はたまたま
It's white and beautiful.
白くて綺麗だなぁ
I'm a little disappointed because I applied too much.
申請すぎてちょっといけない
I'm doing something really bad.
すごいいけないことしてる
I did it with a black tongue, but the old man's tongue started to look like a bloomer.
黒い舌でやったけど、おじさんの舌がブルーマに見えてきた
Do you understand Bruma?
ブルーマ分かる?
I understand.
分 かるよ
The current generation of bloomers is common.
世代的に今のブルーマって通じるんだよ
After all, uncles are still young.
おじさんも青春なんだからね
Is it okay?
いいの?
He's such a good kid.
めちゃくちゃ良い子じゃん
I'm spending half a day there.
半日もんでてるよ
As expected, all the kids I've met so far have said no.
さすがに今までの子みんなダメって言ってる
Today's children are told to hold and sit.
今の子って抱え座りって言ってるよ
It's very picturesque.
すごく絵になるね
Because it's cute.
かわいいから
Uncle doesn't really care, right?
おじさんすごい気にしないでしょ?
Can I count it?
数えていい?
soft.
柔らかい
It's so curvy.
すっごいプリプリしてる
I'm so curvy.
プリプリしてる
The way you smile is cute.
笑い方可愛いね
Your smiling face is cute.
笑ってる顔可愛い
Yeah.
うん
On the other hand, you must be an angel to see me laughing even when I do something like this.
逆にこんなことしても笑ってくれてるのか天使だもんね
Deep black.
深黒
perhaps.
多分
Very cute nearby.
近くめっちゃ可愛い
What kind of sleep do you feel?
どんな寝を感じる?
About normal.
普通くらい
Is it about normal?
普通くらいか
many
多
point.
分
But my voice was a little off.
でも ちょっと声漏れてたね
It felt better than normal.
普通以上に気持ちよくて
I see, it's sexy all at once.
なるほど、一気にセクシーだね
Sextile is really good.
セクスタイルめちゃくちゃ良い
That doesn't work?
あれ、効かない?
this.
これ
I used to say that a long time ago.
昔よく言ってたんだけど
This is the place for people who want to get their hands on it.
手つめたい人はここだったけど
I can do it, but I don't believe it.
手 つくけど、信じてない
Ah, that's right.
ああ、やっぱそうだよね
I just want to fill it up.
ただつめたいだけだもん
Can I apply half weight on these eyes too?
こっちの目も半重で塗れていい?
Okay.
いいよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
He'll forgive you anything.
何でも許してくれるじゃん
You're so kind.
めちゃくちゃ優しいじゃん
The pigment is very pale.
色素めちゃくちゃ薄い
TRUE?
本当?
It's pink.
ピンク色してる
Even if you say uniform hedge, they'll take it off right away.
制服ヘッジって言ってもすぐに脱いちゃうから
surely.
確かに
If you take off your uniform, it will be finished.
制 服を脱いちゃうと仕上がりになっちゃうから
I just noticed it when I touched it a while ago.
ちょっとさっき触ってて気づいたんだけど
Are your pants a little tight?
パンツちょっと締めてない?
I guess so.
そうかなぁ
What do you think?
どうかなぁ?
Can I take a look?
ちょっと見ていい?
picture?
え?
For children who grow well.
伸びが良い子に
Slippery.
ツルツル
picture?
え?
More and more?
もっともっと?
I don't know.
分かんない
Okay, just a little bit, pass this hand through there,
じゃあちょっとね、この手を、そこから通って、
This one also goes through from the bottom and can be expanded a little by yourself.
こっちも下から通って、ちょっと自分で広げられる
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
I just want a little bit.
ちょっとだけ欲しい
It's really dirty.
めちゃくちゃ汚いね
After all, puri is good.
やっぱりプリが良い
Do you like Puri the most?
プリは一番好きかな?
Do you like Puri?
プリ好きなの?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
But, you know, just by putting my finger inside it, it's moving a lot.
でもね、指入れてるだけでめちゃくちゃ中が動いてるんだよね
Because it rolls.
転がるから
転 が る から
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
ち、ち、ちっくり
T-tsk.
ち、ちっくり